<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<document><pre><code># ----------------------------------------
# upgrade-cjk.html
# ----------------------------------------
page = page.next
page.applyTemplate(template)  
page.name = 'Upgrade CJK'
page.url = 'upgrade-cjk.html'

content = page.select('Content')
box = content.newBanner()
</code></pre>

<h1>Upgrade CJK in the making. <a href="downloads/UpgradeCJK_Try.zip">TRY</a> it now.</h1>
<pre><code>box = content.newCropped()
</code></pre>

<p><img alt="y=top h=100% noScale" src="images/IMG_4664.JPG" /></p>
<h1>You &amp; me will have a romantic diner night.</h1>
<pre><code>box = content.newCropped()
</code></pre>

<p><img alt="y=top h=100% noScale" src="images/IMG_4609.JPG" /></p>
<h1>Sweetheart, it’s hotdog time.</h1>
<pre><code>box = content.newIntroduction()
</code></pre>

<h1>TYPE-TRY gives an updated overview of running TYPETR projects. Download sample fonts to test in your designs. Use the type, while it is still in the making. Express wishes and suggestions. Find example templates. Get code snippets that best implement TYPETR type.</h1>
<pre><code>box = content.newBanner()
</code></pre>

<h1>Check out the available scripts</h1>
<pre><code>section = content.newSection()
box = section.newMain()
</code></pre>

<h2>Order the script combinations that you need.</h2>
<p>Ut eget massa aliquam, sagittis dolor vel, efficitur ex. Donec velit tellus, convallis vel porttitor nec, aliquet sed odio. Vestibulum quis diam sit amet mauris elementum posuere quis vitae nisl. Pellentesque nunc mauris, scelerisque id ipsum nec, ultricies commodo arcu. Proin non libero egestas, pretium est sit amet, cursus dolor. </p>
<p>Ut eget massa aliquam, sagittis dolor vel, efficitur ex. Donec velit tellus, convallis vel porttitor nec, aliquet sed odio. Vestibulum quis diam sit amet mauris elementum posuere quis vitae nisl. </p>
<ul>
<li>Mauris sagittis, dui at tristique elementum, sapien tortor accumsan nisi, et blandit eros magna nec arcu. Nulla pharetra rutrum dictum. </li>
<li>Vivamus congue turpis nunc, non vestibulum odio aliquet in. </li>
<li>Aliquam ut dapibus metus, quis vehicula nulla. </li>
<li>Nullam semper erat vel turpis dictum, eget hendrerit mauris convallis.</li>
</ul></document>